[JAO] Our CEO saw your viral confession video.
That was actually one of the deciding factors
on why he said yes to
build a sustainable, mangrove-friendly eco-resort in Cabitoonan.
I almost chose the mangroves over you
[JAO] I know.
But I’m here now.
What matters is we're in this together.
Pearl.
Ariel, I got accepted! I got the scholarship!
Wow! Congratulations!
[SIARGAONON] We’re going to celebrate!
[PEARL] Hi, Sir Han!
Thank you for making me feel that my dreams are valid.
But I also hate you.
For telling me that you like me
then leave without even asking me if I like you back.
[PEARL] I love you, Sir Han.
And it really hurts that you’re not here because I miss you so much.
[PEARL SOBS]
[TANTAN] Sir Handsome!
[JAO] I would like you to meet
the first official hire of Isla Gugma Resort…
Tantan.
[ARIEL] Why won't you let us take you to Manila?
[SIARGAONON] Take care, Princess Pearl.
If you need anything, just text or call, okay?
[HAN BIN] Pearl!
[PEARL] Hey!
When did you get back?
This morning.
I can't miss this for the world.
How's your father?
He has recovered.
And I convinced him that
my sister could take over his business.
But I left my heart here in Siargao.
Sir Han, why aren't you answering your phone calls?
And my text messages?
Did you lose your phone?
[PEARL] But you know what?
Never mind.
‘Cause I’m…
[PEARL] I'm gonna go now.
I got accepted in the scholarship, Sir Han.
I know.
I'm so happy for you.
You're living your dream.
Thank you, Sir Han.
You... You know?
How did…?
You watched the video?
Pearl.
Sir Han.
I know you hate that you love me.
But that's just sad.
Because...
I love that I love you.
[KOREAN] I love you, Pearl.
Sir Han... I love you, too.
[ALON BY JL]
Say hi!
- [ARIEL] Han Bin oppa! - [PA SYSTEM] To our passengers...
- [KARA] Nice to see you! - [PA SYSTEM] this is the boarding announcement ...
- [JAO] Sir Han. - [PA SYSTEM] for flight ...
- [HAN BIN] Jao. - [PA SYSTEM] 2R 925
- [JAO] Good to see you. - [PA SYSTEM] 2R 925
- [ARIEL] When did you arrive? - [PA SYSTEM] to Manila.
- Wait. I think that’s my flight. - [PA SYSTEM] We are now inviting those passengers
- Hug, hug, hug, hug! - [PA SYSTEM] with small children and any...
- [CAROL CRIES] - [PA SYSTEM] passengers requiring special assistance
- [CAROL SNIFFS] - [PA SYSTEM] to begin boarding at this time.
- [PEARL] Okay. - [JAO] Take care, Pearl.
- [PEARL] Bye. - [ARIEL] Take care.
- Mom! Ariel! Kara! - [CAROL] Call every day!
- [JAO] Bye. - [PEARL] Bye!
- [PEARL] Bye! - [PA SYSTEM] Thank you.
[HAN BIN] Pearl!
Before you go,
I have something for you.
Here.
[HAN BIN] It's a little piece of home to remind you of me.
And that you can be confident and that you are never really alone
no matter how far you go.
So, you must remember in Europe,
the food is different.
The sweets, chocolate, they'll be tempting.
So, you’re worried about my cavities?
[HAN BIN CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I'm worried about your smile.
[PEARL LAUGHS]
So, take care of that smile.
[HAN BIN] It's your best weapon!
Never worry about fitting in. Be confident.
Walk into any room like you own it.
I will.
[KOREAN] Thank you.
[JAO] Nice.
[JAO] So, did the plans get delivered to my office?
- [TANTAN] Yes, sir. - [JAO] I need to review them.
[NOAH] Okay, guys, let's take a picture!
[JAO] Photo?
[JAO] Okay.
[JAO] Did you inform Carol we are having lunch there?
- [TANTAN] Yes, sir. - [JAO] Okay, great.
[JAO] At least we can finally get this started, right?
Right, Noah?
[NOAH] Yes, sir.
We're officially starting the Isla Gugma Eco-Resort.
[JAO] We'll be creating a lot of jobs here.
But at the same time, we're staying true to our core values.
By making sure we don't disturb...
and will continue to protect the mangroves here in Cabitoonan, right?
[NOAH] That's right, sir.
[JAO] Kara?
Surprise visit?
[KARA CHUCKLES]
No, I promised Noah I'd come.
Lucky Noah.
You're so dramatic. Of course I came to see you, too.
[KARA CHUCKLES]
So, Sir Paul is really gone?
Uh... Yes, actually, uh…
he was officially fired last week.
All his unprofessional methods and tactics
and all of the things that could have put the name of the company in jeopardy,
all of those information leaked.
Apparently... [JAO CLICKS TONGUE]
an anonymous person snitched.
Anonymous, huh?
Who else knew about his illegal practices?
He had it coming, Kara.
I mean, one of these days, it was bound to happen.
He deserved it.
And it was the right thing to do.
Even though you owed him so much.
But what do you do when someone you owe something to
ends up hurting you?
That person gets cancelled.
He shouldn’t have gone after me, huh?
Well, as long as I'm around, no one can hurt you.
Why don't you just open a security agency?
[JAO CLICKS TONGUE] You're the only one I want to protect.
[KARA AND JAO LAUGH]
[PURE COAST OFFICER ON VIDEO CALL] We share the same advocacies, Caitlyn.
I hope you'll consider the offer, all right?
Thank you so much for the offer.
I'll let you know my decision by Friday.
[PURE COAST OFFICER ON VIDEO CALL] Thank you, Caitlyn.
We're looking forward to working with you here in Denmark,
and wherever Pure Coast has environmental protection programs.
Have a nice day.
You, too. Bye.
[PURE COAST OFFICER ON VIDEO CALL] Bye.
[VIDEO CALL ENDS]
[CAROL SNIFFS]
[CAROL] You know that...
I support you, right?
Whatever your decision is...
Wherever you may go.
[CAROL SNIFFS]
- Oh, Carol. - [CAROL WHIMPERS]
[CAROL CRIES]
I don’t know what I’ll do without you.
[CAROL WHIMPERS AND SNIFFS]
[SIARGAONON] You’re my sister.
[SIARGAONON] We’re sisters.
Mhmm.
[CAROL CRIES]
[CAROL EXHALES]
So…
[CAROL CLAPS]
Okay.
In case it’s cold in Denmark,
so let's pick something out.
- Here. - Are we bringing this?
- Yes. - So pink!
- [CAROL LAUGHS] - Look.
From Pacifico…
- to the world! - [CAROL SQUEALS]
- Miss Siargao! - Your turn, come here.
[CAROL] You can also wear it this way, right?
Makes you go “wow!”
- [CAROL] Now, it’s a shirt. - [KARA] I don’t think so.
- [CAROL LAUGHS] -[KARA] Oh! I don’t think it fits.
- [CAROL] But it does! - [KARA] It does!
[KARA AND CAROL LAUGH]
[KARA] Are you happy?
Yes.
Because I’m finally home.
And everything I need is here.
The island.
You.
And that.
That boat.
- Oh, is that your boat? - [JAO] Yeah.
[KARA] I thought that would take a while?
- We rushed it! - Oh...
Okay.
- Well, you know… - [KARA LAUGHS]
I somehow got to fulfill my mom's dream.
And my dad's, too.
And for little Jao...
who only used to dream.
I’m sure they’re all proud of you.
You’ve come so far,
and you chose to stay.
What about you?
Are you happy?
[WAVES CRASHING]
Kara?
Jao, I'm leaving Siargao.
For…
for vacation?
Kara, you're leaving the island?
[KARA EXHALES]
[KARA BREATHES DEEPLY]
This is hard enough for me.
Please don't make it harder.
Then make me understand.
[JAO] Why?
[KARA EXHALES]
I always say I'll go with the flow.
I'll ride the waves.
But this time...
I'll decide where the flow takes me.
Don't you see a future here in Siargao with me?
[KARA SIGHS]
I thought we loved each other?
And that's true, Jao.
- Don't ever doubt that. - Then don't leave!
If you want to grow, then let's grow together.
Side by side.
Please, Kara. Don't.
Not now.
I'm starting to get to know you more and to love you.
So am I, Jao.
I'm only just getting to know myself, too.
When I moved here,
I decided that I wanted to spend the rest of my life here.
But then I realized this was only the beginning.
[KARA] The island has healed me.
And so did you.
In ways that you will never understand.
You taught me how to breathe again.
To live again.
But as time passes, the more I realize
that there's still something I need to do for myself.
Forgiving...
was only the first part of healing myself.
It wasn't enough for the pain to simply go away.
Because the hardest part...
[KARA SNIFFS]
is figuring out who you are after all that pain.
I won't figure that out if I don't leave the island.
But it's not because you weren't enough.
It's not because I don't love you.
It's because, for the first time in my life,
I'm choosing to know myself completely.
[KARA SNIFFS]
Will this make you happy?
Just know that…
if you ever decide to come back,
I’ll be here. [JAO SNIFFS]
Just find me where you left me.
[JAO] Just like before…
We’ll just go with the flow.
And let the wave take us.
[WOMAN] Did you get hit by the Siargao curse, too?
[KARA] It wasn't a curse.
It was a blessing.
[JAO] I love you, Kara.
[KARA] I love you, too, Jao.
[KARA] Jao, I'm sorry.
[JAO] Love is a curse.
But if you're lucky and you find the right person for you...
here on the island,
the Siargao curse can turn into Siargao magic.
[JAO] Thank you for the inspiration.
Because of it, I finally found where I belong.
[NOAH] Caitlyn!
The two community leaders are on their way here.
They want to personally thank you.
Where are you going?
Siargao.
Have you been?